A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, 2008-2018 (bulk 2014-2018)
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Correspondence and Supporting Documentation, Office of the Secretary, 2008-2018., Extent: 11 boxes (3.85 cu. ft.). (Box 11-21)
  - Subseries B: Subject files
    Subseries B: Subject files, 2008-2018, is housed in seven boxes and contains budgets, clippings, correspondence, meeting agendas, memorandum, notes, press releases, reports, and other sundry materials. This series includes information on issues such as animal shelters, the Chesapeake Bay Foundation, Dept. of Forestry reforestation and regulations, horse racing and the Virginia Racing Commission, gaming and fantasy sports, invasive insects and plants, local industries, and wine growers and sales, among others.
    - Agency executive agreements, 2014 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - AFID, Guidelines and best practices, 2014 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Agribusiness Council, 2012-2015 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Animal shelters, 2015-2016 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Assateague Island, 2015-2016 (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
    - Atlantic Coast Pipeline, 2016 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Bingo, Virginia Charitable gaming, 2014-2016 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Broadband Advisory Council, 2015 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Budget, 2014-2018 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
    - Cattlemen's Association, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2013-2015 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Chesapeake Bay Program, Livestock exclusion, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Chesapeake Bay Program, Management Board, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Chesapeake Bay Program, Reports, 2013-2014 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Chesapeake Bay Program, Scientific and Technical Advisory Committee, 2013-2014 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Chesapeake Bay Program, WIP Milestones, 2013-2014 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - China, 2012-2014 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Cider sales tracking, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Colonial Downs, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Commodity check off meeting, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, Reports, 2012-2013 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Delaware Young Farmer, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Dutch biomass issue, 2014 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Dutch-Woodpellet visit, 2015 November (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Elks, VDACS, 2015 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - EPA Roundtables, 2014 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Executive orders, 2014-2015 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Fantasy sports, 2016 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Farm Bureau, Shareholders notes, 2016 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - First Lady of Virginia, 2016 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Food freedom, 2008-2015 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Food safety, 2014 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Board meeting, 2015 September (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Bourassa State Forest, 2011-2014 (Box 17, Folder 13-15)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Bourassa State Forest, 2011-2014 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Conservation and Acquisitions, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Dinner, 2015 September (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Forest products, 2014-2015 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Information Technology, 2013 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Legislation, Reforestation Operations Fund, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Legislation, State FOrest Activity Fee, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Matthews State Forest, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Organizational charts, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Plum Creek, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Reforestation of timberlands, 2013 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Regulations, 2011-2014 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Regulations, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Silvicultural Regulatory Consistency Act, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Resource Management Plan, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 15-16)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Resource Management Plan, 2013-2014 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Restructuring, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Riparian Forest Tax Credit Legislation, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Special Use Permit Regulations, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Stanley Land and Lumber, ca. 2012 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Stream Mitigation Banks (HB 1168), 2014 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Sustainability talking points, 2014 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Timber theft, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, Truck weights, 2014-2015 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Dale Gardiner meeting, 2015 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Great Meadow Foundation, Inc., 2014 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - House Bills, 2016 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Invasive Species Working Group, 2015 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Judge Justice Roush, 2015 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Loudoun Breweries, ca. 2015 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Lyme Disease Task Force, 2015 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Mid-Atlantic State Agriculture Secretaries and Commissioners meeting, 2015 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Moldova, 2014 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Noxious weeds, 2015 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Nutrient Credit Reform, 2016 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Oyster Company of Virginia, 2015 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Paradise Springs Winery, 2014-2015 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Perdue Agribusiness PMT, 2014 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Preservation Virginia, 2015 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Press releases, 2011-2013 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Purchase of development rights, 2015 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Senate Finance Committee, Subcommittee on Economic Development, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Smithfield, ca. 2014 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Stakeholders meeting notes, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - State Fair, 2015 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Suffolk Intermodal Project, 2015 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Tranlin, Inc., 2015 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Agricultural Council, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Bio-Tech Roundtable, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Dept. of Agricultural and Consumer Services, Slowly-available Nitrogen Study, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Forestry Association, 2014-2015 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Horse Center, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Horse Center Foundation, 2014-2015 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation, 2014-2015 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Poultry Foundation, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Racing Commission, 2013-2014 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Racing Commission, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Racing Commission, 2015 (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
    - Virginia State University, Field Day, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Wine Council-Virginia Grain Producers, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Wine, Amazon, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Wine Region Signs, 2011-2012 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Working Lands Investment Partners, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Series IV: Economic Development, 2009-2016., Extent: 7 boxes (2.45 cu. ft.). (Box 22-28)
  Series IV: Economic Development, 2009-2016, is housed in seven boxes and arranged chronologically. The series documents the Secretary's involvement with economic development and tourism projects, initiatives, and events, as well as interactions with outside economic development and tourism businesses, organizations, boards, and commissions. This series includes correspondence, itineraries, briefings, invitation lists, newspaper clippings, press releases, speeches, notes, and reports. A large portion of this series includes various marketing and trade mission trips to the East and West coasts of the United States; countries such as Cuba, Israel, and India; and throughout Asia and Europe. Also included are visits to Virginia from various ambassadors. Trade issues, such as China's ban on U.S. poultry, and Virginia agribusinesses, such as wineries, cider and beer breweries, seafood, and peanuts, were major topics of discussion. Since Secretariat Todd Haymore served both Governor McDonnell and Governor McAuliffe, the records span both governorships.
  - Cuban Trade Mission, 2009 November 1-7 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - London Trade Mission, 2010 May 15-20 (Box 22)
  - Europe Trade Mission, 2010 July 17-24 (Box 22, Folder 3-5)
  - Cuban Trade Mission, 2010 November 2-5 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Asian Trade Mission, 2011 May 6-17 (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
  - Asian Trade Mission, 2011 May 6-17 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Cuban Trade Mission, 2011 November 2-4 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Trade Mission to India and Israel (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - West Coast Trade Mission, 2012 March 26-28 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Marketing Mission to New York City and Montreal, Canada, 2012 April 10-13 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - European Trade Mission, 2012 June 11-20 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - European FAM (Friends and Family Open Party) Tour, 2012 September 14-19 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Cuban Trade Mission, 2012 November 4-7 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Craft Breweries, 2012 December 6 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Tech-Hops and Barley Research, 2012-2014 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Marketing Mission to Los Angeles, San Francisco, China, and Tokyo, 2013 April 10-26 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - London, 2013 June 18-22 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Perdue Agribusiness Visit, 2013 August 13 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Columbia and Panama Trade Mission, 2013 September 15-20 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Cuban Trade Mission, 2013 November 4-7 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Canada Trade Mission, 2013 November 19-21 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Deep Water Rail-Served Terminal Sites (Port of Virginia), 2013 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Portsmouth Marine Terminal, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Perdue Agribusiness Visit, 2014 February 7 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Fujian, China, 2014 February 21-22 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Local Food Access Meeting, 2014 February 25 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Ambassador Baucus (U.S. Ambassador to China), 2014 March 9 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - VEDP, Economic Development Collaborative, 2014 April 22 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Marketing Mission to Chicago, 2014 May 13-14 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - London International Wine Fair, 2014 June 2-3 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - San Diego Bio Convention-Trade Mission, 2014 June 23-25 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Marketing Mission to China and United Kingdom, 2014 July 9-17 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Pittsylvania County-Danville Meeting, 2014 September 8 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Sanderson Farms, 2014 September 12 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Japanese Peanut Buyers Reverse Trade Mission, 2014 September 22 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - New York Marketing Mission, 2014 October 6-8 (Box 25, Folder 6-7)
  - Asian Marketing Mission, 2014 October 18-29 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Asian Marketing Mission, 2014 October 18-29 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Cuban Trade Mission, 2014 November 3-6 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Rockingham County Fairgrounds Poultry Project, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Strategic Plan, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Cuban Trade Mission, 2015 January 3-6 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Ambassador of Republic of Paraguay, 2015 February 9 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - European Union Ambassador David O'Sullivan, 2015 February 10 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Italian Ambassador Bisogniero, 2015 February 16 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Ballast Point Brewing and Spirits, 2015 February 19 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Ambassador Serdar Kilic of Republic of Turkey, 2015 February 26 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Czech Republic Agriculture Delegation Meeting, 2015 March 24 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Craft Beer Reception, 2015 April 13-16 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - London Trade Mission, 2015 May 6 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Meeting with Swedish Ambassador Bjorn Lyrvall, 2015 May 26 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - European Trade Mission, 2015 June 8-19 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - West Coast Marketing Mission, 2015 September 14-17 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - VCU-Cuba Meeting, 2015 September 17 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Marketing Mission to Quebec and Ontario, Canada, 2015 September 23-24 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Ambassador of Kuwait, 2015 November 6 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Belgian Ambassador Johan Verbeke, 2015 November 12 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - United Arab Emirates and India Marketing Mission, 2015 November 13-24 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Visit with Uzbekistan Ambassador Gulyamov, 2015 December 15 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Trade Mission Planning, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Hanover Messe and Europe Marketing Mission, 2016 April 23-29 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Boston, Montreal and Toronto Marketing Mission, 2016 May 17-20 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Israel and Farnborough Airshow Marketing Mission, 2016 July 8-13 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Columbia Agricultural Trade and Marketing Mission, 2016 August 16-19 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Columbia Agricultural Trade and Marketing Mission, 2016 August 16-19 (Box 28, Folder 1-3)
  - Chicago Marketing Mission, 2016 September 13-14 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Series V: Public Relations, 2010-2018., Extent: 12 boxes (4.1 cu. ft.). (Box 29-40)
  Series V: Public Relations, 2009-2016, is housed in twelve boxes and arranged chronologically. The series documents the Secretary's various public relations events and meetings. This series is very similar and even duplicates some of the materials from Series IV: Economic Development. The series includes agendas, briefing information, brochures, correspondence, minutes, notes, press releases, power point presentation slides, speeches. Includes visits from Ambassadors, trade mission to promote investment in the Commonwealth, increase exports of agricultural products, board of directors meetings,
  - Cabinet retreat, 2010 January 7-8 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Agribusiness Council Town Hall Meeting, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 1a)
  - Governor's Conference on Agricultural Trade, 2012 March 13-14 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Agribusiness Council Town Hall Meeting, 2012 September-October (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Wine Board, Marketing, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Conference on Agricultural Trade, 2013 March 7-8 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Hopewell Ethanol Project, 2013 September 13 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Project Cavalier, 2013 September 26 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Strategic Review of Agricultural Education, 2013 October 31 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Governor-Elect Transition, 2013 December 6 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Aqua Moaf, 2013-2014 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Chrysalis Vineyards, 2013 (Folder 11)
  - Vireol Bio Energy, Ltd., 2014 January 30 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Ambassador Ahn [South Korea], 2014 January 30 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Young Farmers Conference, 2014 February 9 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - USDA Meeting, 2014 February 11 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Virginia International Business Council, 2014 February 26 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Governor's Cup Gala, 2014 February (Box 29, Folder 16a)
  - Ag Export Meeting, 2014 March 11 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Trade Mission Briefing, 2014 March 11 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Ferrum College Conference, 2014 March 12 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - VEDP Board of Directors, 2014 March 12 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Joint Declaration between France and Virginia, 2014 March 13 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Ambassador Mike Froman [United States], 2014 March 14 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Wine Board Meeting, 2014 March 17-18 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Richmond Ballet, Road to China, 2014 March 19 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Minister Lu Kang Meeting, 2014 March 19 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Golden Agribusiness Day, 2014 March 21 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - GMU Presentation, 2014 March 25 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Food and Beverage Expo, 2014 March 26 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Wine and Dine Society Fair, 2014 March 27 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Council on Virginia Future, 2014 April 1 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Consul of Mexico, 2014 April 1 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Delegation-UVA Panel, 82014 April 1 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Forestry Summit, 2014 April 4 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Project Cavalier, 2014 April 7 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation, 2014 April 9 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Monticello Wine Trail Cup Awards, 2014 April 10 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Qatar, 2014 April 13 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Strauss Group, 2014 April 17 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Nutriati-Virginia Bio Tech Park, 2014 April 23 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Wine Board Meeting, 2014 April 24 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Export-Import Bank Annual Conference, 2014 April 24 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - VCU Executive MBA, 2014 April 25 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Tech International Trade Seminar, 2014 April 28 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Corsi Group, 2014 April 29 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Procure Con, 2014 April 30-May 1 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Agriculture Census Report, 2014 May 1 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Virginia State University Cooperative Extension Forum, 2014 May 7 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Maritime International Trade Symposium, 2014 May 8 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Forestry Resources Association Board Meeting, 2014 May 9 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Wine Board Meeting, 2014 May 12 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Richmond Ballet, 2014 May 16 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Forest Day, 2014 May 20 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Branding the Virginia Oyster, 2014 May 21 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Evening at Mt. Vernon, 2014 May 21 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Tobacco Commission, 2014 May 21-22 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Ambassador Ashok Mirpuri [Singapore], 2014 June 3 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - VEDP Board Meeting, 2014 June 5 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - State Depts. of Agriculture, 2014 June 8-11 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - SASDA Conference, 2014 June 9 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Delmarva Poultry Industry, Board of Directors Meeting, 2014 June 10 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Hardwood Check Off, 2014 June 17 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - VADD Meeting, 2014 June 18 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - CITNA [Chinese Tobacco International Inc.] Meeting, 2014 June 18 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Ambassador Sasae [Japan], 2014 June 18 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Perdue Granary [Kinsale, Va.], 2014 June 19 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Congressman Cliff Sterns, 2014 June 19 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Relay Foods AFID Announcement, 2014 June 30 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Ambassador Lyushun Shen [Taiwan], 2014 July 8 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Walmart Conference Call, 2014 July 17 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Revitalization of Virginia Railway System, 2014 July 22 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - JTI Meeting, 2014 July 23 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - USA Invest Co., 2014 July 23 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services Meeting, 2014 July 28 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Farmers Market, 2014 August 7 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Precision Agriculture, 2014 August 12 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Oyster Visits, 2014 August 13 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Association of Counties, Officials Summit, 2014 August 14 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Dept. of Forestry, 100th Anniversary Reception, 2014 August 18 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Oyster Trail Announcement, 2014 August 19 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Japan Tobacco Inc. Meeting, 2014 August 19 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Wine Council, 2014 August 20 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Craft Beer Reception, 2014 August 22 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Ambassador Peter Wittig [Germany], 2014 August 22 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Agribusiness Industry Roundtable, 2014 August 25 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Wine Tasting, 2014 August 25 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Wine Board Meeting, 2014 August 26 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - VFPA [Virginia Forest Products Association] Annual Convention, 2014 September 5-7 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - CCTV America Interview, 2014 September 10 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - VEDP Board Meeting, 2014 September 11 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Ambassador Ahn [South Korea], 2014 September 16 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Racing Commission Meeting, 2014 September 17 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Ambassador Ndabashinze [Burundi], 2014 September 18 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - University of Kentucky, 2014 September 22 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Consul General of Italy, 2014 September 22 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Charitable Gaming, 2014 September 23 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - CACLWG [Comprehensive Animal Care Law Working Group], 2014 September 24 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Diner 85th Anniversary, 2014 September 25 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - CEO's Dinner, 2014 September 25 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - DuCard Love Sign Unveiling, 2014 September 26 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Virginia State Fair, 2014 September 29 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - USDA Press Conference, 2014 September 29 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture and Forestry Roundtable, 2014 September 29 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Cuban Interest Section Meeting, 2014 September 30 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - US IPA [Industrial Pellett Association] Conference, 2014 October 2 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Capitol Peak Brochure, 2014 October 6 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Principals Staff Committee Follow-Up, 2014 October 6 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - VEDA Fall Conference, 2014 October 9 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Hopewell-Prince George County Chamber of Commerce, 2014 October 9 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Ambassador Tiankai [China], 2014 October 14 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Director Wen-ling Wu [Taiwan], 2014 October 14 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - VLCF [Virginia Land Conservation Foundation] Board of Trustees, 2014 October 20 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Wine and Brine Weekend, 2014 November 7-9 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Ambassador Bisogniero [Italy], 2014 November 10 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Williams Mullen Ag Event, 2014 November 12 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Vine Meeting, 2014 November 12 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - VFPA [Truck Weights], 2014 November 12 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - VDACS Policy Planning, 2014 November 12 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Bold Rock Cider Grand Opening, 2014 November 13 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Ag Spotlight with Delegate Garrett, 2014 November 17 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Ambassador Cuisia [Philippines], 2014 November 20 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Eastern Shore Ag Conference, 2014 November 20 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Bridging the Nutritional Divide, 2014 November 20 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Salisbury Country Club Wine, 2014 November 21 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Enviva, 2014 November 24 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Virginia Wine Board Meeting, 2014 December 2 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Virginia Asian Chamber Gala, 2014 December 2 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - VAFB [Virginia Farm Bureau Federation] Annual Meeting, 2014 December 3 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Capitol Christmas Tree Lighting, 2014 December 5 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - VCU Beta Alpha Psi Luncheon, 2014 December 5 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Delegate Chris Jones, 2014 December 8 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - VDACS Board Meeting, 2014 December 11 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - VEDP Board Meeting, 2014 December 11 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Ambassador Ahn [South Korea], 2014 December 16 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Visit to Loudoun County, 2014 December 16 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - The FarmTable.org, 2014 December 18 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Human Rights Watch, Child Labor, 2014 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - UVA Cancer Center, 2015 January 9 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Algenetix, 2015 January 12 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Esquire Magazine Dinner, 2015 January 12 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - VAC [Virginia Agribusiness Council] Agribusiness Dinner, 2015 January 15 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - VADO [Virginia Ag Development Officers] Meeting, 2015 January 15 (Box 34, Folder 13a)
  - VAC Agribusiness Dinner, 2015 January 15 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Regional Conservation Partnership Program, 2015 January 16 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - HAC [House Appropriations Committee] Ag Subcommittee, 2015 January 21 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Beach City Manager, 2015 January 22 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Atlas Comms, 2015 January 27 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - SFC [Senate Finance Committee] Ed Subcommittee, 2015 January 27 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - GMU [George Mason University] School of Public Policy, 2015 January 28 (Box 34, Folder 20)